isport.com 2019-09-16

# Privacy Policy at SwimOutlet.com

**Effective Date: November 1, 2018**

Welcome to SwimOutlet.com, which is owned and operated by Spiraledge, Inc. d/b/a SwimOutlet.com (" **SwimOutlet** " " **we** " or " **us** "). We understand that your privacy and the protection of your data are important to you. We created this Privacy Policy to help you understand the types of information we collect about you through the SwimOutlet.com website (the " **Site** "), why we collect, how we use it, and when we share it with third parties. We also describe the choices have about how we collect and use your information. 

Because your privacy also matters to us, please take your time reviewing this Privacy Policy. As you review, keep in mind that if you use the Site, you consent to our collection and handling of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and made part of our Terms of Use, which we also encourage you to review because they contain important limitations on our liability to you.

**If you do not agree with any provision of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site or submit your information to us.**

If you have questions about our Privacy Policy, please contact us using the information below. You may use the following links to navigate our Privacy Policy and learn more about our data practices:

  * What kinds of Information do we collect?
  * How do we use this information?
  * How is this information shared?
  * Cookies and other Data Collection Technologies
  * How can I manage or delete information about me?
  * How can I opt out of marketing communications?
  * How do we protect your information?
  * Links to third party websites
  * Note to international users
  * Your California privacy rights
  * Children's privacy
  * How will we notify you of changes to this Privacy Policy?
  * How to contact us

**WHAT KINDS OF INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?**

Depending on how you use the Site, we may collect different kinds of information from or about you:

  * **Information you provide:** We collect the content and information you provide when you use the Site, including when you create a SwimOutlet.com account (" **Account** "); participate in a survey, contest, sweepstakes, or other promotion; register for our newsletter; post a review of a purchase, provide us with feedbacks, comments, and testimonials; or request information or assistance from us. Your content and information may include " **Personal Information** ", which is any information that can be used to identify for you. For example, Personal information can include your: 
    * Contact information (name, address, phone number, or email address);
    * Photo or images;
    * Certain data about your use of the Site that is considered Personal Information in some jurisdictions; and
  * User comments that you may provide, such as in reviews, blog posts, testimonials, or comments. Please note that the information you submit in these user comments may be posted publicly on the Site. If you do not want your information to be publicly available, please do not submit reviews, testimonials, or comments. 
  * **Device Information:** We collect information from or about the computers, phones, or other devices that you use to access the Site. We may associate this Device Information across your devices, which helps us provide consistent services across your devices. Such device information typically includes: 
    * Your online environment (operating system, browser, hardware version, device settings, or device identifiers);
    * Device location, including specific geographic locations, such as through Bluetooth, WiFi signals, or GPS;
    * Connection information (name of your mobile operator, internet service provider, IP address); and 
    * Browsing activity, such as the pages you visit or the links you click on.
  * **Payment Information:** If you place an order, we will collect the information that we need to process your transaction, such as your name, billing address, shipping address, phone number, and the recipient's information if the order is a gift. We have engaged a company called "Authorize.net" (www.authorize.net) to help us process your payment card information securely. We do not store any of your financial or credit card information. If you provide us with your phone number you may opt-in to receive text messages containing updates on your order. 
  * **Social Media Account Information:** If you choose to connect your social media account to the Site, the social media platform may share information with us about your use of the social media platform. This information may include your profile information such as name and email address.. Please refer to that social media platform's privacy settings to control how your information is share with us and other third parties. 
  * **Employment Application Information:** If you apply for employment with SwimOutlet.com, we will collect your name, work history, and other information relevant to your employment application. We will not use your information for purposes other than evaluating and processing your employment application.

**HOW DO WE USE THIS INFORMATION?**

We are passionate about creating engaging and customized experiences for you and we use all of the information we collect to help provide and support the Site. We also use your information to communicate with you and deliver advertising that may be more relevant to you. We will obtain your consent to use your Personal Information for a purpose other than as described in this Privacy Policy and below: 

  * **Offering, improving and developing the Site:** We use your information to provide and improve the services that we offer, including to operate, maintain and develop Site content, features, and products. We also use your information to analyze our operations and marketing initiatives and develop new services and products in response to your feedback. We also may use the data to track user behavior (e.g., pages viewed, for how long, the performance of those pages, etc.) to improve the product/service and user experience.
  * **Communicate with you:** We may use your information to send you marketing communications, surveys, and important administrative announcements about the Site or your Account. We also use your information to respond to you when you contact us. 
  * **Personalize your experience:** Your information helps us personalize your experience when you use the Site. We use your information to present to you products and information tailored to your interests and provide you with specialized content and product offers. For more information about how you can control how information about you is used to personalize the ads you see, please see the section on Opting out of Interest-Based Advertising below. 
  * **Promoting Safety and Security:** We use the information we collect to help verify your identity, your account, and your activity on the Site. We might use this information, for instance, to investigate suspicious activity or violations of our Terms of Use or policies. 

We use cookies and other data collection technologies to provide and support the Site and the uses outlined and described in this section of the Privacy Policy. See Cookies and Other Data Collection Technology below to learn more about how we use Data Collection Technology and how to control cookies on your devices.

**HOW IS THIS INFORMATION SHARED?**

We will only share your Personal Information we disclosed to you at the time we collect it, with your consent, or as stated below: 

  * **With our vendors:** We work with vendors that help us provide you the Site and related services. Unless prohibited by applicable law, we may share information with our vendors for purposes such as website hosting, professional services, human resources management, customer service, e-mail delivery and auditing. When we share Personal Information with vendors, we require those vendors to process your Personal Information only on our behalf and for the same purposes for which the Personal Information was collected. 
  * **With third party partners:** We work with third party partners that provide advertising, measurement and analytics services. We want our advertising to be relevant and interesting, so we may share information with these third party partners to help us tailor these advertisements to your interests. We do not share Personal Information with these third party partners, nor do we sell or lease your Personal Information to any third parties for such third party's marketing purposes.
  * **With affiliates:** We share Information within our corporate family for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy and as required or authorized by law. Affiliates are those companies that are under common control of Spiraledge, Inc., which is the primary data controller for these purposes. 
  * **As part of a corporation transaction:** Unless prohibited by applicable law, we may share, transfer or delete your Personal Information if we are involved in a merger, sale, acquisition, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, bankruptcy or other change of ownership or control by SwimOutlet or any affiliated company (in each case, whether in whole or in part). If required by applicable law, any such sharing of information will be reported to regulators in accordance with the applicable law. 
  * **In other lawful ways:** We may also share your Personal Information: (i) if we determine that disclosure is necessary to comply with the request of a law enforcement, regulatory agency or other legal process; (ii) to protect the rights, privacy, property, interests or safety of our company or our affiliates, customers, business partners, suppliers, employees or the general public; (iii) to pursue available remedies or limit damages; (iv) to enforce our Terms of Use; (v) to respond to an emergency; and (vi) as otherwise permitted by applicable law.

**COOKIES AND OTHER DATA COLLECTION TECHNOLOGY**

We use cookies and other data collection technologies to help us provide, protect and improve the Site.

**Cookies** are small pieces of text used to store information on web browsers. Cookies are used to store and receive identifiers on computers, phones and other devices and they may contain information such as user settings, browsing history and other Internet activities. While the cookies that we use may change from time to time as we improve and update the Site, the types of cookies we use generally fall into the below categories: 

  * **Session Cookies** are used to operate our Services. Some cookies are essential for the operation of the Services. If a user chooses to disable cookies, certain content and features may not be available. 
  * **Preference Cookies** are used to remember your preferences. For example, when you select your location on Site, we use cookies to remember your location preferences so you do not have to select it every time you visit the Site. 
  * **Advertising Cookies** are used to serve you with advertisements that we believe are relevant to you and your interests. These cookies also help us evaluate our marketing program performance and analytics. 
  * **Security Cookies** are used for general security purposes, such as user authentication and preventing fraudulent use or unauthorized access of data.

We also use **web beacons** (also called a pixel tag or clear GIF) that enable us to monitor user activity and website traffic. To learn more about cookies and web beacons, visit [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/ "www.allaboutcookies.org"). In this Privacy Policy, we refer to cookies, web beacons, and other similar technology as " **Data Collection Technology**." 

**Why we use Data Collection Technology:** Data Collection Technology helps us to save your password for future log-ins, detect and prevent fraud, and help us (and our ad partners) manage our online marketing program and deliver ads that are relevant or may be of interest to you. Data Collection Technology also helps us personalize and improve the performance of the Site. For example, we use Google Analytics to collect information to improve the Site, such as how often users visit a website, what pages they visit when they do so, and what other website they used prior to visiting the Services. Google Analytics places a cookie on your web browser so that it can identify you the next time you visit the Site, the cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google. Google's ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to the Site is restricted by the [Google Analytics Terms of Use](https://www.google.com/analytics/terms/ "Google Analytics Terms of Use") and the [Google Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy "Google Privacy Policy"). 

**Controlling cookies on your computer:** We will notify you when you are on part of the Site that uses cookies. By continuing to use that part of the Site after such notice, you accept the use of cookies. If you do not wish to receive cookies, you may set your browser to reject cookies or alert you when a cookie is dropped on your computer. Usually, these settings are available through the security features of your web browser. Please be aware that if you disable cookies, some features on the Site may not be available.

**Our policy on "Do Not Track" signals:** California's Online Privacy Protection Act requires website operators to disclose how they respond to web browser's "Do Not Track" (" **DNT** ") signals. Some web browsers incorporate a DNT or similar feature that signals to websites that a user does not want to have his or her online activity tracked. Not all browsers offer a DNT option and DNT signals are not yet uniform. For this reason, many website operators, including SwimOutlet, do not respond to DNT signals.

**Opting out of Interest-Based Advertising.** Interest-based advertising is a way that helps companies provide you with more relevant advertising on the websites you visit of the applications you use. If you want to "opt out" of receiving online interest-based ads, please follow the instructions at [www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices "www.aboutads.info/choices"), or <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>. Please note that when you "opt-out" of receiving interest-based ads, this does not mean you will no longer see ads from us or on the Site. It means that the online ads that you do see will not be based on your particular interests. If you delete cookies on your device, generally you will need to opt-out again. More information about online behavioral advertising can be found at [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/ "www.aboutads.info").

**HOW CAN I MANAGE OR DELETE INFORMATION ABOUT ME?**

If you are an Account holder, you can manage your Personal Information in your account settings and profile page. Depending on where you live, you may have legal rights to access, modify, or delete the Personal Information we hold about you. Exercise such rights must be in accordance with applicable law, and we reserve the right to charge appropriate fees to respond to such request if permitted by applicable law. To exercise these rights or delete your account, please contact us by using the contact information set forth in the How to Contact Us section below. 

**HOW CAN I OPT OUT OF MARKETING COMMUNICATIONS?**

If you do not wish to receive marketing-related emails from us or prefer us not to process your Personal Information for marketing purposes, you may use the unsubscribe link in any of our marketing emails or contact us at **1-800-691-4065** or **shop@swimoutlet.com**. Please note we cannot remove your Personal Information from the databases of third parties (who are not our vendors) with whom we have shared your Personal Information prior to your opt-out request. Please contact those third parties directly.

**HOW DO WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION?**

We take reasonable precautions intended to help protect your Personal Information that we collect. Unfortunately, no system or online transmission of data is completely secure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data transmitted across the Internet. If you believe that information you provided to us is no longer secure, please notify us immediately using the contact information provided below.

**LINKS TO THIRD PARTY WEBSITES**

The Site may include links to third party websites and services that we do not own or operate. When you click these links, you will be directed away from the Site to that third party's website. Any information you submit on that third party's website will be subject to that third party's practices and privacy policy. We encourage you to read these third party privacy policies carefully before submitting your information.

**NOTE TO INTERNATIONAL USERS**

Please note that your Personal Information may be stored and processed on servers in the United States. The laws on holding personal data in the United States may differ from the laws of other countries. By using the Site, you consent to the transfer, storage and use of your Information in accordance with applicable laws and with this Privacy Policy. 

**YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACYRIGHTS.**

Under California law, California residents have the right to request a list of all third parties to whom a company has disclosed their Personal Information for those third parties' direct marketing purposes. We do not currently share Personal Information with third parties for those third parties marketing purposes; however, if you are a California resident and would like information on how to exercise your rights concerning third party disclosures, please contact us at **privacy@swimoutlet.com**.

**CHILDREN'S PRIVACY**

The Site is not directed to or intended for use by minors. Consistent with the requirements of the U.S. Children's Online Privacy Protection Act and similar rules in other jurisdictions, if we learn that we have received any information directly from a child under age 13 (or such other age as set by the laws of jurisdictions outside the U.S.) without his or her parent's verified consent, we will use that information only to respond directly to that child (or his or her parent or legal guardian) to inform the child that he or she cannot use the Site and subsequently, we will delete that information..

**HOW WILL WE NOTIFY YOU OF CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY?**

The Effective Date of this Privacy Policy is set forth at the top of this page. If we make a material change to the way we treat your Personal Information, we will notify you in advance via email or through the Site. Your continued use of the Site after the Effective Date of any changes constitutes your acceptance of the amended Privacy Policy. Any amended Privacy Policy supersedes all previous versions. 

**CONTACT US**

To learn more about how SwimOutlet and uses your information, please contact us using the information below: 

By Mail:  | 

Spiraledge, Inc.d/b/a Swimoutlet.com  
1919 S. Bascom Ave, Ste 300  
Campbell, CA 95008  

---|---  
By Phone: | 

1-800-691-4065

By Email:  | 

**legal@swimoutlet.com**
